<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <ATR_MechanicalStandardization.label>Mechanical standardization</ATR_MechanicalStandardization.label>
  <ATR_MechanicalStandardization.description>In order to reach a state of consistent manufactured quality and scaling quantity, a standard of production and maintenance must be established. Androids come in a vast number of styles and designs - standardizing the colony's parts will be critical for success in mechanical fields.</ATR_MechanicalStandardization.description>

  <ATR_InterchangeableParts.label>Interchangeable parts</ATR_InterchangeableParts.label>
  <ATR_InterchangeableParts.description>The standardization of designs, components, and assembly techniques allows for the standardization of parts, and thus, interchangeability. Dedicating resources to designing easily replaceable, upgradeable parts will open up new avenues for specialization and efficiency gains.</ATR_InterchangeableParts.description>

  <ATR_StandardizedCommunications.label>Standardized communications</ATR_StandardizedCommunications.label>
  <ATR_StandardizedCommunications.description>Standardizing communication and digital presence technologies will allow a baseline for a network of connected mechanical units and devices. The advent of a theoretical cloud environment connecting those consciousnesses and devices could allow for great opportunities for insights into shared experience, security, or remote attacks on hostile entitites. It all begins with infrastructure.</ATR_StandardizedCommunications.description>

  <ATR_MechanicalStimulators.label>Mechanical stimulants</ATR_MechanicalStimulators.label>
  <ATR_MechanicalStimulators.description>While mechanical units are largely unconcerned by the passage of time and therefore unconcerned about the efficiency of its use, there are times when efficiency at a particular moment is critical. Consumable short-term stimulants could prove useful in these moments.</ATR_MechanicalStimulators.description>

  <ATR_AdvancedMechParts.label>Advanced mechanical parts</ATR_AdvancedMechParts.label>
  <ATR_AdvancedMechParts.description>With the acquisition of properly fabrication and a strong standardization scheme, advancements in the quality of mechanical parts is now within reach. These parts will function significantly better than factory standard equivalents while remaining within reasonable cost estimates.</ATR_AdvancedMechParts.description>

  <ATR_MechanicalFrameworks.label>Basic framework replacements</ATR_MechanicalFrameworks.label>
  <ATR_MechanicalFrameworks.description>The framework of a mechanical unit is its most visible feature, as it quite literally holds the entire chassis together. Basic modifications could result in significant gains in a wide range of particular tasks - but does require committing to one particular modification at a time.</ATR_MechanicalFrameworks.description>

  <ATR_MechaniteAssistedRecovery.label>Mechanite assisted recovery</ATR_MechaniteAssistedRecovery.label>
  <ATR_MechaniteAssistedRecovery.description>While simple components and replacement parts can fix most physical damage to mechanical units, recovering the consciousness of a sapient mechanical entity is a more complicated process. Advanced tools and and intricate materials - with the technical knowhow to produce and incorporate - will be required to reactivate offline mechanical sapients.</ATR_MechaniteAssistedRecovery.description>

  <ATR_RemoteControlProtocols.label>Remote control protocols</ATR_RemoteControlProtocols.label>
  <ATR_RemoteControlProtocols.description>With standardized communication methods across hosts, it is theoretically possible to develop a framework for remotely controlling so-called surrogate bodies. Technical limitations prevent organic involvement in this service due to a lack of efficiency and universal organic applications, but this could prove revolutionary for mechanical units.</ATR_RemoteControlProtocols.description>


</LanguageData>